https://www.ensemble.com.au/privacy/

Buy tickets Read more see more Privacy Policy Home | Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyINTRODUCTIONBy providing personal information to us, including by purchasing tickets and subscriptions from us, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any other arrangements that apply between us. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time by publishing changes to it on our website. We encourage you to check our website periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current Privacy Policy. PRIVACY PRINCIPLESEnsemble Theatre is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We understand and appreciate that patrons are concerned about their privacy, and the confidentiality and security of any information that may be provided to us. This Privacy Policy outlines our obligations to you in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs).The APPs regulate the manner in which we handle, use and manage your personal information from initial collection to use and disclosure, storage, accessibility and disposal. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONEnsemble Theatre will only collect your personal information where and when it relates to performances and other products, services and opportunities offered to you.The personal information we may collect includes, amongst other things:your name, address and other contact detailspayment details such as credit card detailsproof of age, such as your date of birth or qualification for a concessionemail addressgeographic locationtransaction details relating to your use of our products and servicesany preferences you notify to usany other personal information that may be required in order to facilitate your dealings with usWe may collect this information:when you register on our websitewhen you, or a person on your behalf, purchase tickets, subscriptions or gift vouchers to our theatre productionswhen you attend an Ensemble Theatre performancewhen you subscribe to our newsletterwhen you donate to us or otherwise support Ensemblewhen you communicate with us through correspondence, mail, phone, face to face contact, email, or using our website ‘Contact Us’ functionalitywhen you interact with our website, services, content and advertisingfrom our trusted partners, including third party suppliers and service providersWe may also collect your personal information if you are, or are employed by, our production partners, organisations that hire our venues, our suppliers (including service and content providers), contractors, agents and other partners.In addition, when you apply for a job or position with us we may collect certain information from you (including your name, contact details, working history and relevant records checks) from any recruitment consultant, your previous employers and others who may be able to provide information to us to assist in our decision on whether or not to make you an offer of employment or engage you under a contract. This Privacy Policy does not apply to acts and practices in relation to employee records of our current and former employees, which are exempt from the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONWhenever Ensemble Theatre collects personal information from you we will make every reasonable attempt at the time to inform you:why we are collecting your informationto whom we will disclose your informationof the purpose(s) for which we intend to use your informationWe may collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for the following purposes:contacting you in the event of a performance cancellation or change in detailsnotifying you of changes in performance detailsreplacing lost ticketsresponding to your requestsproviding recommendations or information about upcoming performances, specials and offers at Ensemble Theatreengaging with you in relation to, and providing you information about, donations and other philanthropic opportunitiesidentifying ways in which we can provide you with a better service or enhance your experience with Ensemble Theatrenotifying you of events that we think may be of interest to youfor such further and other lawful uses in connection with Ensemble Theatre activities consistent with this Privacy Policy.Ensemble Theatre may disclose your personal information to third parties that help us operate our business or provide a service to you including contractors and service providers that:work with us to produce theatre workshelp us operate our computer systems including ticketing services and the provision of hosted servicessend out our mail/emails and clean collected dataperform data analysis to group demographic attributes of individuals, including so that we may direct programs, philanthropic opportunities or initiatives provided by Ensemble that may appeal to you.If you do not want to receive marketing materials from us, please opt-out via the opt-out facilities provided in the relevant communication (e.g. an unsubscribe link). Alternatively, you may contact us using the details set out below.Ensemble does not sell your personal information to any third parties unless expressly agreed otherwise. DATA QUALITY AND SECURITY Ensemble Theatre keep records of the personal information we gather from you, including via electronic storage, storage in the cloud, on our servers and secure physical records. At all times, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is protected, treated confidentially and guarded from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure and we use a number of physical, administrative, personnel and technical measures to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.Ensemble Theatre will not store your information overseas for any purpose. ACCESS TO AND CORRECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONAt all times, we will take great care to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete and up to date. If you wish to access or correct the personal information that we hold about you, please set out your request in writing by contacting us using the information below, including your phone number and email address.Sometimes, we may not be able to provide you with access to all of your personal information and, where this is the case, we will tell you why. We may also need to verify your identity when you request your personal information.If personal information held by us is shown not to be accurate, complete and up to date, we will take reasonable steps to correct those deficiencies.Should Ensemble Theatre decline your request, we will provide you with reasons for refusal. COOKIESAs our website uses cookies, you must ensure that your web browser is set to allow cookies. Most web browsers are set by default to accept cookies to enable us to display targeted interest-based advertising on a variety of websites. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to either prompt or refuse cookies. Please note that rejecting cookies may disable your browser from purchasing tickets on our website. DISPOSAL OF YOUR INFORMATION If we no longer require your personal information, unless we are required under Australian law or a court or tribunal order to retain it, we will take reasonable steps to destroy, securely delete, or de-identify it. CONTACT USFor further information about our Privacy Policy or practices, or to access or correct your personal information, or make a complaint, or to opt-out of direct marketing, please contact our Privacy Officer using the details set out below:Ensemble Theatre 78 McDougall Street Kirribilli, NSW 2061 AustraliaEmail: boxoffice@ensemble.com.auPhone: (02) 8918 3400
2021 SEASON SUBSCRIBE NOW 2021 SeasonAboutBayly’s BistroDiscoverDevelopmentEducationWork with usSUPPORT USYour SafetyGift VouchersContact Login Basket Join Newsletter
